You just flipped the table and restarted
It's true
Just married
What are you smiling at
My friends are asking if I'm Mrs Fu
Incomplete answer
You're Fu Chenyan's wife
Status just confirmed
Aren't you afraid people will say I married up
Says who
People online definitely will
Then let Fu Corp's legal team
Warn them to watch their words
Mr Fu
You're really acting like the heir now
I'm just protecting my wife
Mr and Mrs Fu
The Chairman is asking if you two
Are staying for dinner tonight
You decide
We'll stay
Are you scared
A little
But I dared to swap grooms at my wedding
Dinner with the Fu family should be fine
Hmph Mrs Fu is very bold
Mingyao really made the right choice this time
She didn't just pick the right person
She also got the contract right
Ah